<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Me on Lina Avendaño</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/tags/about-me/</link><description>Recent content in About Me on Lina Avendaño</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:01:26 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/tags/about-me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beyond Work: Passion for Creativity &amp; Culture</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/gallery/hobbies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:01:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/gallery/hobbies/</guid><description>&lt;p>While my professional background is deeply rooted in &lt;strong>finance, accounting, and business strategy&lt;/strong>, I have always believed that true fulfillment comes from engaging in &lt;strong>passions that inspire and energize me&lt;/strong>. Two of my greatest personal pursuits are &lt;strong>Kaufhaus der Anden&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>my passion for painting&lt;/strong>, both of which allow me to express creativity, appreciation for culture, and a connection to craftsmanship.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="kaufhaus-der-anden-a-passion-project-with-purpose">&lt;strong>Kaufhaus der Anden: A Passion Project with Purpose&lt;/strong>&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Kaufhaus der Anden is more than a business to me, it is a &lt;strong>labor of love&lt;/strong>, a space where I bring together &lt;strong>handmade, cultural, and eco-friendly&lt;/strong> products from the &lt;strong>Andean region&lt;/strong>, from my favourite and most beautiful places. While it is a business that should be profitable, I see it primarily as a &lt;strong>platform for artisans and small entrepreneurs&lt;/strong>, ensuring that their craftsmanship reaches a wider audience. Running KDA is not about financial dependence but about &lt;strong>curating something meaningful&lt;/strong> that reflects my passion for culture, sustainability, and ethical commerce.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>