<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Customer Service on Lina Avendaño</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/tags/customer-service/</link><description>Recent content in Customer Service on Lina Avendaño</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/tags/customer-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Online Fashion Entrepreneurship</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience7/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="founder--owner--kaufhaus-der-anden-germany">&lt;strong>Founder &amp;amp; Owner – Kaufhaus der Anden, Germany&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="2023--present">2023 – Present&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://kaufhaus-der-anden.com">Kaufhaus der Anden&lt;/a> is my own entrepreneurial venture, a &lt;strong>multi-brand platform&lt;/strong> that brings together &lt;strong>handmade, cultural, and eco-friendly&lt;/strong> products from the &lt;strong>Andean region&lt;/strong>. As the &lt;strong>founder and owner&lt;/strong>, I oversee every aspect of the business, from &lt;strong>product sourcing and supplier partnerships&lt;/strong> to &lt;strong>financial management, marketing, and customer experience&lt;/strong>. This business is more than just an eCommerce store; it is a &lt;strong>platform that highlights artisans and small entrepreneurs&lt;/strong>, ensuring their craftsmanship reaches a wider market.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ERP Software Implementation</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience5/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="odoo-expert--xoe-corp-sas-bogotá-colombia">&lt;strong>Odoo Expert – XOE CORP. SAS, Bogotá, Colombia&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="aug-2017--mar-2020">Aug 2017 – Mar 2020&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>My journey into &lt;strong>ERP systems and digital transformation&lt;/strong> took off in this role, where I became an &lt;strong>Odoo specialist for accounting and payroll solutions&lt;/strong>. I helped companies &lt;strong>optimize their financial processes&lt;/strong> by configuring and implementing &lt;strong>ERP solutions&lt;/strong>, training teams, and ensuring that financial management was &lt;strong>efficient and compliant&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, I developed and led the &lt;strong>BPO division for accounting and payroll&lt;/strong>, an experience that enhanced my ability to &lt;strong>analyze business needs, customize ERP solutions, and improve workflow automation&lt;/strong>. This role reinforced my belief that &lt;strong>technology can revolutionize financial management&lt;/strong>, making processes more &lt;strong>transparent, accurate, and scalable&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>