<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lina Avendaño</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/</link><description>Recent content on Lina Avendaño</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Real Estate Accounting</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience1/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="property-accounting-manager--res-familiae-arnold-gbr-germany---part-time">&lt;strong>Property Accounting Manager – Res Familiae Arnold GbR, Germany - Part Time&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="aug-2023--present">Aug 2023 – Present&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>I originally started working for this business in &lt;strong>2018&lt;/strong> and stayed for about a year, but due to time constraints, I had to step away. However, when my family and I moved to &lt;strong>Germany in 2023&lt;/strong>, they gave me the opportunity to &lt;strong>rejoin the company&lt;/strong>, allowing me to pick up where I left off and apply my enhanced expertise.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Online Fashion Entrepreneurship</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience7/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="founder--owner--kaufhaus-der-anden-germany">&lt;strong>Founder &amp;amp; Owner – Kaufhaus der Anden, Germany&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="2023--present">2023 – Present&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://kaufhaus-der-anden.com">Kaufhaus der Anden&lt;/a> is my own entrepreneurial venture, a &lt;strong>multi-brand platform&lt;/strong> that brings together &lt;strong>handmade, cultural, and eco-friendly&lt;/strong> products from the &lt;strong>Andean region&lt;/strong>. As the &lt;strong>founder and owner&lt;/strong>, I oversee every aspect of the business, from &lt;strong>product sourcing and supplier partnerships&lt;/strong> to &lt;strong>financial management, marketing, and customer experience&lt;/strong>. This business is more than just an eCommerce store; it is a &lt;strong>platform that highlights artisans and small entrepreneurs&lt;/strong>, ensuring their craftsmanship reaches a wider market.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Accounting, Finance, and Management</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience2/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="finance-and-accounting-manager--pristina-company-sas-remote">&lt;strong>Finance and Accounting Manager – Pristina Company SAS, Remote&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="mar-2023--jan-2025">Mar 2023 – Jan 2025&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Joining this company was an opportunity to &lt;strong>reshape financial operations&lt;/strong> from the ground up. My biggest accomplishment has been leading the &lt;strong>implementation of the company’s first ERP system&lt;/strong>, transitioning financial management from &lt;strong>Excel-based processes to a fully integrated digital platform&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I oversee &lt;strong>financial reporting, cash flow management, and tax compliance&lt;/strong>, ensuring that the company maintains transparency and efficiency. Additionally, I have developed a structured &lt;strong>document archiving system&lt;/strong> to improve regulatory compliance and financial analysis. The role has allowed me to refine my &lt;strong>analytical and process-optimization skills&lt;/strong>, proving that smart financial management can &lt;strong>drive better decision-making and business stability&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Food Service Entrepreneurship</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience3/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="typical-restaurants--founder--business-owner-bogotá-colombia">&lt;strong>Typical Restaurants – Founder &amp;amp; Business Owner, Bogotá, Colombia&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="feb-2021--jul-2022">Feb 2021 – Jul 2022&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Starting my own restaurant was one of the most &lt;strong>challenging and rewarding experiences&lt;/strong> of my career. It was not just about running a business—it was about &lt;strong>transforming an idea into a thriving operation&lt;/strong>. I took charge of everything from &lt;strong>financial planning and marketing strategies to operations and customer service&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Through a &lt;strong>data-driven approach&lt;/strong>, I optimized &lt;strong>inventory management, pricing strategies, and supplier negotiations&lt;/strong>, which led to a &lt;strong>150% increase in sales&lt;/strong>. A strong focus on &lt;strong>brand identity and social media marketing&lt;/strong> helped us grow to over &lt;strong>4,000 followers in just three months&lt;/strong>. Additionally, I successfully implemented &lt;strong>cost control measures and efficiency improvements&lt;/strong> that made the business sustainable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CEO</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience4/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="head-of-branch--8bit-group-bogotá-colombia">&lt;strong>Head of Branch – 8Bit Group, Bogotá, Colombia&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="sep-2017--dec-2019">Sep 2017 – Dec 2019&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Building something from scratch has always been my passion, and this role was exactly that—a chance to &lt;strong>establish and lead an entire eCommerce operation&lt;/strong> from the ground up. Within just three months, I helped &lt;strong>set up a local subsidiary of a Russian company&lt;/strong>, overseeing key areas such as &lt;strong>finance, accounting, HR, fulfillment, logistics, and customer service&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Managing sales of up to &lt;strong>$30,000 per day&lt;/strong>, ensuring the timely delivery of over &lt;strong>1,500 packages daily&lt;/strong>, and leading a &lt;strong>250-person team&lt;/strong> required &lt;strong>strong leadership, problem-solving, and strategic decision-making&lt;/strong>. I negotiated contracts with &lt;strong>last-mile delivery companies&lt;/strong>, developed &lt;strong>new product lines&lt;/strong>, and implemented &lt;strong>KPIs across all areas&lt;/strong>, boosting efficiency by &lt;strong>50%&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ERP Software Implementation</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience5/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="odoo-expert--xoe-corp-sas-bogotá-colombia">&lt;strong>Odoo Expert – XOE CORP. SAS, Bogotá, Colombia&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="aug-2017--mar-2020">Aug 2017 – Mar 2020&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>My journey into &lt;strong>ERP systems and digital transformation&lt;/strong> took off in this role, where I became an &lt;strong>Odoo specialist for accounting and payroll solutions&lt;/strong>. I helped companies &lt;strong>optimize their financial processes&lt;/strong> by configuring and implementing &lt;strong>ERP solutions&lt;/strong>, training teams, and ensuring that financial management was &lt;strong>efficient and compliant&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, I developed and led the &lt;strong>BPO division for accounting and payroll&lt;/strong>, an experience that enhanced my ability to &lt;strong>analyze business needs, customize ERP solutions, and improve workflow automation&lt;/strong>. This role reinforced my belief that &lt;strong>technology can revolutionize financial management&lt;/strong>, making processes more &lt;strong>transparent, accurate, and scalable&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Accounting and Management Support</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:40:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/experience/en/experience6/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="executive--business-manager--el-alemán-sas-bogotá-colombia">&lt;strong>Executive &amp;amp; Business Manager – El Alemán SAS, Bogotá, Colombia&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="jan-2016--aug-2017">Jan 2016 – Aug 2017&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>This role gave me the &lt;strong>full spectrum of business management experience&lt;/strong>. I was responsible for &lt;strong>finance, HR, inventory, procurement, manufacturing, and sales&lt;/strong>, leading a &lt;strong>cross-functional team&lt;/strong> and ensuring the company operated efficiently.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of my key achievements was &lt;strong>opening the company’s first store&lt;/strong>, which involved handling everything from &lt;strong>market analysis and logistics to financial planning and supplier negotiations&lt;/strong>. Managing &lt;strong>payroll, imports, and financial reporting&lt;/strong>, I developed a &lt;strong>holistic view of business operations&lt;/strong>, strengthening my ability to &lt;strong>connect finance with strategy&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hi-my-name-is-lina-avendaño-and-i-come-from-colombia">Hi, my name is Lina Avendaño, and I come from Colombia&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I’ve always been someone who loves numbers, strategy, and problem-solving, but at the same time, I enjoy creativity, culture, and new challenges. My career has taken me through &lt;strong>finance, accounting, technology, and entrepreneurship&lt;/strong>, where I’ve had the chance to help businesses &lt;strong>optimize their financial operations, make smarter decisions, and use technology to work more efficiently&lt;/strong>. I’ve worked in &lt;strong>corporate finance, real estate accounting, eCommerce, IT, and business leadership&lt;/strong>, gaining experience across different industries and learning how to adapt and grow.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Employment</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/employment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:18:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/employment/employment/</guid><description>&lt;p>Over the years, I have built a career that blends finance, accounting, business management, and technology, allowing me to develop a strategic and analytical mindset while staying adaptable to different industries. From leading financial operations and optimizing business processes to implementing ERP systems and running my own company, my experience has been shaped by challenges, growth, and the drive to make an impact.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please have a look to each one of my work experiences:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Download my CV</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/download/downloadmycv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:17:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/download/downloadmycv/</guid><description/></item><item><title>LinkedIn</title><link>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/linkedin/linkedin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:17:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://lina2358.github.io/myCV/page/linkedin/linkedin/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>